export const chapter = "Chapter -15: Adverbs";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What does an adverb add to the meaning of?",
          optionA: "Noun",
          optionB: "Verb",
          optionC: "Adjective",
          correctAnswer: "Adjective",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The bird sang sweetly,' what part of speech is 'sweetly'?",
          optionA: "Adjective",
          optionB: "Adverb",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "Adverb",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following words is an adverb of frequency?",
          optionA: "Almost",
          optionB: "Never",
          optionC: "Most",
          correctAnswer: "Never",
        },
        {
          question: "How are many adverbs of manner formed?",
          optionA: "By adding -ing to verbs",
          optionB: "By adding -ly to adjectives",
          optionC: "By removing the last letter of adjectives",
          correctAnswer: "By adding -ly to adjectives",
        },
        {
          question: "What do adverbs of time show?",
          optionA: "Where an action takes place",
          optionB: "How often an action takes place",
          optionC: "When an action takes place",
          correctAnswer: "When an action takes place",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Come here,' what part of speech is 'here'?",
          optionA: "Adjective",
          optionB: "Adverb",
          optionC: "Noun",
          correctAnswer: "Adverb",
        },
        {
          question: "Which sentence contains an adverb of place?",
          optionA: "I speak the truth always.",
          optionB: "She finished the work yesterday.",
          optionC: "We climbed up the stairs.",
          correctAnswer: "We climbed up the stairs.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What kind of adverbs show how often an action takes place?",
          optionA: "Adverbs of Place",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Manner",
          optionC: "Adverbs of Frequency",
          correctAnswer: "Adverbs of Frequency",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an adverb modifying an adjective in the given sentences?",
          optionA: "Quite",
          optionB: "Forward",
          optionC: "Yesterday",
          correctAnswer: "Quite",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does the adverb 'never' indicate in the sentence 'She has done it quite nicely'?",
          optionA: "Manner",
          optionB: "Frequency",
          optionC: "Place",
          correctAnswer: "Frequency",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "An adverb is a word that adds to the meaning of an __________.",
          optionA: "Noun",
          optionB: "Adjective",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "Adjective",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of manner show the ________ an action takes place.",
          optionA: "Time",
          optionB: "Frequency",
          optionC: "Manner",
          correctAnswer: "Manner",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of time indicate __________ an action takes place.",
          optionA: "How often",
          optionB: "Where",
          optionC: "When",
          correctAnswer: "When",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of place demonstrate __________ an action is done.",
          optionA: "How often",
          optionB: "Where",
          optionC: "When",
          correctAnswer: "Where",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Many adverbs of manner are formed by adding ________ to adjectives.",
          optionA: "-ing",
          optionB: "-ly",
          optionC: "-ed",
          correctAnswer: "-ly",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of frequency or number show ________ an action takes place.",
          optionA: "How often",
          optionB: "Where",
          optionC: "When",
          correctAnswer: "How often",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs can modify adjectives, verbs, or other ________.",
          optionA: "Nouns",
          optionB: "Adverbs",
          optionC: "Prepositions",
          correctAnswer: "Adverbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs add something to the meaning of an adjective, a verb, or another ________.",
          optionA: "Adjective",
          optionB: "Adverb",
          optionC: "Noun",
          correctAnswer: "Adverb",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of frequency show ________ an action takes place.",
          optionA: "When",
          optionB: "How often",
          optionC: "Where",
          correctAnswer: "How often",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an adverb modifying an adjective in the given sentences?",
          optionA: "Quite",
          optionB: "Forward",
          optionC: "Yesterday",
          correctAnswer: "Quite",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Adverbs of manner indicate where an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of frequency show how often an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of time express the manner in which an action occurs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs can modify adjectives, verbs, or other adverbs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The primary purpose of adverbs is to modify nouns.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of place indicate where an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of frequency show when an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Many adverbs of manner are formed by adding -ly to adjectives.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of time express the frequency of an action.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs add something to the meaning of adjectives, verbs, or other adverbs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
